JONEER SLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

ABOUT ME

I am a crypto/blockchain enthusiast and Web3 Developer. My focus is on leveraging my software development skills and applying them to Web3. I am a chronic open-source contributor and have a lot of experience with distributed collaboration. Along with my full-time Blockchain Development role I have experience developing for the EVM, Solana & Flow blockchains.

EXPERIENCE

JAMBB

BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

Architects, maintains, and deploys smart contracts and decentralized applications to meet the needs of hundreds of thousands of fans. Tech: Docker, Node.js, Cadence, Solidity, Hardhat, IPFS, Nuxt, Vue, Tailwind, Git, TypeScript. Jan 2022 - Present

VARIOUS ORGANIZATIONS

OPEN SOURCE SOFTWARE CONTRIBUTOR

Develops and delivers software solutions to over 20 organizations including The Ethereum Foundation, Mozilla, #VetsWhoCode, Apache & more. Tech: Docker, Node.js, EJS, Tailwind CSS, Markdown, Git, Angular, TypeScript, JSON, SCSS, React. Oct 2020 - Present

FARM BUREAU BANK

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Responsible for the development and maintenance of internal and external web applications and tools. Writes, tests, develops and implements custom programs to streamline financial institution workflows. Tech: jQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL. May 2019 - Jan 2022

CNF TECHNOLOGIES

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (CONTRACT)

Responsible for developing and maintaining the full stack of a website utilized by the U.S. Air Force to maintain and track data on cryptographic products. Tech: ASP.NET, jQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL DataTables, Bootbox, Font Awesome & Bootstrap. Mar - Dec 2018

CONTACT

kevinjones.engineer github.com/joneskj55 linkedin.com/in/joneskj55 joneskj55@gmail.com

EDUCATION

BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY

2020 - 2022 | BS Web Development

CODEUP

2016 - 2017 | Full-Stack Web Development Certificate

SKILLS

JavaScript Git
TypeScript CSS
Node.js HTML
Vue.js Ethers.js
Cadence Web3.js
Solidity Hardhat